

- +91 97470 73452
- rafeekpkd@gmail.com
- Palakkad, Kerala, India

## **EDUCATION**

Master of Business Administration (Finance)

**Bharathiyar University**Coimbatore

Bachelor of Commerce with computer application (B.com Ca)

Mount Seena arts & science collage Palakkad, Kerala

# **EXPERTISE**

Financial Analysis
Strategic Planning
Regulatory Compliance
Software Proficiency
Auditing and Internal Controls
Client Relationship Management
Process Optimization
Cash Flow Management
Financial Reporting

## **LANGUAGE**

English Hindi Malayalam Tamil

# MOHAMMED RAFEEK K

Accountant cum Administrator

#### **ABOUT ME**

Willing to take up responsible position with any reputed firm that will be utilized to strengthen the organization inAccounting and Administration areas where I can contribute my knowledge and skills secured through experience, hard work and motivation to form a full-fledged project team. I trust in success of hard work and dedication in service with full confidence.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Oct 2019 - Present

Arabian delight events and caters | Palakkad, Kerala Chief Accountant cum Administration

Proven track record as Chief Accounts cum Administrator at Arabian Delight Events and Caterers, demonstrating expertise in financial management, strategic planning, and administrative leadership. Successfully ensured regulatory compliance, optimized processes, and fostered effective team collaboration.

Nov 2018 - Jan 2019 Corass Builder's and Developer's LLC

#### Accountant

Accomplished Accountant with valuable experience at a leading construction and development firm. Proficient in financial management, regulatory compliance, and meticulous financial reporting. Adept at optimizing processes to contribute to the company's financial success.

2014 - 2018

Top Notch Bakers Group | Palakkad, Kerala Assistant Accountant cum Administrative Assistant

I Diligent Assistant Accounts cum Administrative Assistant with experience at a prominent bakery group in Palakkad, Kerala. Demonstrated proficiency in financial tasks and efficient administrative support. A reliable contributor to streamlined operations and team collaboration.

#### REFERENCES

Mr. Yousuf
MD | Arabian Delight

Phone: +91 9846633824

Mr. Rizwan

Managing Partner | Top Notch Bakers

6633824 Phone: +91 9633244999